Hoh, hmm, hmm, hmm
Kettle and Idol
Yes, it has a "*".
I wrote "reading" to make it sound like I'm a smart, capable, and capable girl.
So I wrote it with an "*" and diluted it a little.
I've never been good at reading since I was a child, and reading has always been my weak point.
I realized how important it is to read the printed word. When I read scripts, there are kanji that I can't read.
When I read scripts, there are kanji I can't read, or when I can't read a few words.
I realized that I needed to read more.
I started reading books when I was about 20 years old.
And recently
I've been reading books since I was about 20 years old.
all of my knowledge comes from reading.
I've come to enjoy reading.
I think this is a very important point for me these days.
So this is an opportunity for you to advance more and more now.
Yes, I've started to read a variety of books.
How do you find new books to read?
Well, I don't really read novels or stories.
I tend to read books for the purpose of learning or studying.
I tend to read books for the purpose of learning or studying. I tend to read books for the purpose of learning or studying.
When I'm struggling to understand why I can't do something, I search for the word and find it.
I often search for the word and pull it up.
I often search for the word and read and study it.
Lately, I've been trying to get better at making small talk.
I read somewhere that the best people
I heard that the best people who can do a good job are good at making small talk.
I wanted to be able to do it.
I looked up words like "the ability to make small talk.
I read a lot of books about how to ask good questions.
I found a book called "How to Ask Good Questions of the Best".
I bought those books and read them.
I try to copy what I can.
I see.
What else has left an impression on you?
Is there any other book that really stood out to you?
When I decided to read.
The first book I read was a famous book called "The Courage to Be Unlikable.
I couldn't even get to page 10 until I read that one.
Until then, I couldn't even get to page 10,
I was having a problem at the time of wanting to be liked by everyone, and I felt like a weak person,
I was struggling with my weak self that wanted to be liked too much, and that's when it clicked,
I thought it was really interesting, and I kept reading and reading.
I see.
How many books do you have on your bookshelves now?
How many?
But I'm a slow reader.
There are not many shelves.
I'm on the third shelf now.
It's starting to accumulate.
Maybe someday...
I'm a minimalist.
I don't have a lot of things in my room.
I'm a minimalist and I don't have a lot of stuff in my room.
I'll fill the walls with books
I want to study so many things
I want to make my room smart.
I hope you will say good-bye to the camera with a few words of endearment.
Yes, ma'am.
This show is called
Nuka-chan
Aya-chan, I love you, Okichi-san, Hakushaku-san
Mr. Asahi
Yui-san
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much